Total paragraphs: 880
Main content starts at: 34
Closing starts at: 876
Content paragraphs: 842

Found 846 content paragraphs

=== ALL CONTENT ===
1. You may qualify as a successor in interest if an ownership interest in the property located at [M567] (New Property Line 1/Street Address), [M583] (New Property Unit Number), [M568] (New Property Line 2/City State and Zip Code) was transferred to you
2. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = AL, AZ, AR, CA, CO, DE, FL, GA, ID, IL, IN, IA, KS, KY, LA, ME, MD, MA, MI, MN, MS, OH,OR, PA, RI, SD, TN, TX, VT, VA, WA,WV,WI,WY THEN:
3. A transfer by devise, descent, or operation of law on the death of a joint tenant or tenant by the entirety.
4. To prove borrowerÆs death:
5. Death Certificate
6. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = CO THEN:
7. Supplementary Affidavit
8. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = CA THEN:
9. Affidavit of death of Joint Tenant with attached Death Certificate
10. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = AL, AZ, AR, CA, CO, DE, FL, GA, ID, IL, IN, IA, KS, KY, LA, ME, MD, MA, MI, MN, MS, OH, OR, RI, SC, SD, TN, TX, UT,VT,VA,WA,WV,WI,WY THEN:
11. To prove your identity:
12. Valid Government Issued ID
13. To prove that you were transferred an ownership interest in the borrowerÆs property:
14. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = WY THEN:
15. Method of Transfer: Declaration of Trusts, Affidavit of Survivorship, Deed with Life Estate
16. Trust or
17. Deed or
18. Affidavit of Survivorship with Certified copy of Death Certificate
19. Method of Transfer: Probate, Summary Probate
20. Will or
21. Decree of Distribution or
22. Decree of Summary Distribution
23. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = WI THEN:
24. Method of Transfer: Nonprobate
25. Form HT-110 or
26. Deed and Death Certificate
27. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = WV THEN:
28. Method of Transfer: Probate
29. Last Will and Testament or
30. Intestacy
31. Method of Transfer: Nonprobate
32. Death Certificate and Deed
33. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = WA THEN:
34. Method of Transfer: Probate (assuming no joint tenancy)
35. Personal RepresentativeÆs Deed
36. Certified Copy of Decree of Distribution
37. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = VA THEN:
38. Method of Transfer: Probate and Filing a list of heirs with the Circuit Court
39. Will filed with the probate court
40. List of heirs that supports fact of death and listing of heirs
41. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = VT THEN:
42. Method of Transfer: Non-probate
43. Deed and Death Certificate or
44. HeirÆs Deed
45. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = TX THEN:
46. Method of Transfer: Probate
47. Probate Court Orders filed in real property records of county in which property is located or
48. Distribution Deeds
49. Method of Transfer: Non-probate
50. Affidavit of Heirship
51. Transfer on Death Deed
52. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = UT THEN:
53. Method of Transfer: Non-probate
54. Affidavit of Heirship
55. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = TN THEN:
56. Method of Transfer: Automatically for Joint Tenant or Tenants by the Entirety
57. This process occurs automatically by operation of law. Please sign the acknowledgement form in order for Triad Financial Services, Inc. to confirm your status as a successor in interest.
58. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = RI, SC, SD THEN:
59. Method of Transfer: Non-probate
60. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = RI, SC THEN:
61. Death Certificate (tenants in common presumed unless joint tenancy declared in deed)
62. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = SD THEN:
63. Affidavit of Survivorship
64. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = PA THEN:
65. Method of Transfer: Non-probate
66. Deed or
67. Death Certificate or
68. Affidavit and Notice of Appraisal from Department of Revenue as proof Inheritance Tax was paid.
69. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = OR THEN:
70. Primary Method of Transfer: Non-Probate
71. Recorded Death Certificate
72. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = OH THEN:
73. Method of Transfer: Probate/Administration
74. Order of the Probate Court and the filing of a Certificate of Transfer
75. Method of Transfer: Non-Probate
76. Affidavit of Surviving Spouse
77. Joint Tenant & Death Certificate
78. Affidavit for Transfer & Record of Real Estate Inherited
79. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MI THEN:
80. Primary Method of Transfer: Tenants in Common
81. Documents evidencing the transfer include a Deed from the Personal Representatives of the Estate of the Deceased or a Court Order
82. Primary Method of Transfer: Joint Tenants
83. Recording of a Certified Copy of the Death Certificate of the Deceased
84. Primary Method of Transfer:  Tenancy by the Entireties
85. Recording of a Certified Copy of the Death Certificate for the Deceased spouse
86. A deed from less than all tenants named in the instruments which created the tenancy will not be accepted as conveying full marketable title in the absence of record proof of the death of each such tenant who does not join the Deed.
87. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = AL, AZ, CA, IN, KY, LA, ME, MD, MN THEN:
88. If the primary method of transfer was probate then any of the following will suffice:
89. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MN THEN:
90. Affidavit of Identity and Survivorship & Certified Copy of Death Certificate
91. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MD THEN:
92. Deed (All MD Deeds must be signed by a MD lawyer or a party to the deed)
93. The personal representative of the estate needs to present to the clerk of Circuit Court deed must recite the personal representativeÆs position and the estateÆs case number.
94. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = LA THEN:
95. Judgement of Possession in a succession proceeding
96. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = AL, AZ, CA, ME THEN:
97. Deed of Distribution (Formal Administration), or
98. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = AL, AZ, CA THEN:
99. Order of Summary of Administration (Summary Administration), or
100. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = AL, AZ, CA THEN:
101. Order Determining Homestead (Summary Administration or Formal Administration)
102. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = IN, KY, ME THEN:
103. Personal Representative Deed/ Affidavit
104. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = KY THEN:
105. Method of Transfer: Joint Tenancy with Right of Survivorship
106. Death Certificate
107. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = AL, AZ, CA, DE, FL, GA, ID, IL, KS, ME, MA, MS THEN:
108. If the primary method of transfer was non-probate then the following will serve as proof:
109. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MS THEN:
110. Deed to Trustee accompanied by Trust
111. Memorandum/ Certificate of Trust
112. Will
113. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = ME THEN:
114. Affidavit containing the following:
115. Legal Description
116. Recording information establishing Joint Tenancy
117. Name of deceased and surviving tenants
118. Certified Copy of Death Certificate
119. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = KS THEN:
120. Affidavit of Death filed with the register of Deeds (The affiant should be a responsible person who knows the facts)
121. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = AL, AZ, CA, IN THEN:
122. Deed signed by the owner or grantor with a survivorship provision.  If there is no will, you will need to provide 2 heirship affidavits from disinterested parties.
123. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = DE THEN:
124. Combined Affidavit of Joint Property/ No Estate Tax, Original Will, if any
125. Deed
126. Note: In Delaware when property is acquired by husband and wife there exists a presumption that the property is held as tenancy by the entirety, however since the Courts will look to the original intent of the parties the deed should make clear that 
127. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MA THEN:
128. Record a Certified or Authenticated Copy of a Death Certificate
129. If registered land, affidavit of no divorce must be included
130. If registered land, the Land Court Guidelines be reviewed and followed
131. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = FL, ID THEN:
132. Affidavit of Survivorship or
133. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = FL THEN:
134. Deed of Distribution or
135. Order of Summary Administration or
136. Order determining Homestead
137. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = GA THEN:
138. Affidavit
139. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = IL THEN:
140. Deceased Joint Tenancy Affidavit
141. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = AL, AZ, AR, CA, CO, DE, FL, GA, ID, IL, IN, IA, KS, KY, LA, ME, MD, MA, MI, MN, MS, MT, NE, NV, NH, NJ, NM, NY, ND, OH, OK, OR, PA, RI, SC, SD, TN,TX, UT, VT, VA, WA,WV,WI,WY THEN:
142. A transfer to a relative resulting from the death of a borrower;
143. To prove borrowerÆs death:
144. Death Certificate
145. To prove your identity:
146. Valid Government Issued ID
147. To prove that you were transferred an ownership interest in the borrowerÆs property:
148. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = WY THEN:
149. Method of Transfer: Declaration of Trust, Affidavit of Survivorship, Deed with life Estate
150. Trust or
151. Deed or
152. Affidavit of Survivorship with certified copy of Death Certificate
153. Method of Transfer: Probate, Summary Probate
154. Will or
155. Decree of Distribution
156. Decree of Summary Distribution
157. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = WI THEN:
158. Method of Transfer: Nonprobate
159. If held in trust during life, you will need a TrusteeÆs Deed
160. If designated as a Transfer on Death,  you will need Form 110 or and an Affidavit
161. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = WV THEN:
162. Method of Transfer: Probate
163. Last Will and Testament
164. Intestacy
165. Joint Ownership with Right of Survivorship
166. Method of Transfer: Nonprobate Transfer on Death Deed and Certificate
167. Transfer on Death Deed (Must state that a transfer to a designated beneficiary is to occur at the transferorÆs death)
168. Death Certificate
169. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = WA THEN:
170. Method of Transfer: Non-probate
171. For real property
172. Death Certificate and Affidavit of Survivorship
173. For personal property
174. Death Certificate and form required by bank or other entity
175. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = VA THEN:
176. Method of Transfer: Probate, Trustee under a revocable trust, Filing a list of heirs with the circuit court
177. Will filed with probate court or
178. Deed recorded of record or
179. List of heirs form filed
180. Method of Transfer: Transfer on Death Deed
181. The Last Will and Testament or
182. List of Heirs or
183. Certificate of Trust or
184. Transfer on Death Deed
185. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = VT THEN:
186. Method of Transfer: Probate
187. Deed and Death Certificate or
188. Probate Court Order
189. Method of Transfer: Non-probate
190. HeirÆs Deed
191. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = TN THEN:
192. Method of Transfer: Probate
193. Order of Probate Court granting Letters of Testamentary of letters of Administration
194. Method of Transfer: Small Estates Procedure, Probate as Muniment of Title
195. Certified copy of Affidavit as to small estate or
196. Copy of Order Admitting Will to Probate as a Muniment of Title
197. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = TX THEN:
198. Method of Transfer: Probate
199. Order Admitting Will to Probate as a Muniment of Title or
200. Distribution Deed from Executor/Administrator having been granted letters
201. Small Estate Affidavit
202. Order Declaring Heirship
203. Method of Transfer: Non-probate
204. Affidavit of Heirship
205. Transfer on Death Deed
206. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = RI,UT, SC, SD THEN:
207. Method of Transfer: Probate (Assuming no joint tenancy)
208. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = RI,UT THEN:
209. Deed of Distribution & Certificate of Descent or Distribution signed by fiduciary and recorded
210. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = UT THEN:
211. Certified copy of Decree of Distribution
212. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = SC THEN:
213. Deed of Distribution with respect to real property
214. Appropriate Instrument of Conveyance with respect to personal property
215. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = SD THEN:
216. Deed of Distribution
217. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = PA THEN:
218. Method of Transfer: Probate
219. Will
220. Deed
221. Probate Documents (Letters) and Notice of Appraisal from Department of Revenue as proof Inhertiance Tax was paid
222. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = OR THEN:
223. Method of Transfer: or Small Estate Affidavit
224. Personal Representatives Deed or
225. AffiantÆs or claiming SuccessorÆs Deed
226. (An heir or devisee, as a "claiming successor," may file a small-estate affidavit with the clerk of the probate court in any county having venue for a probate proceeding. ORS 114.515(1) A small-estate affidavit must include (1) a statement that "reas
227. Method of Transfer: Transfer on Death Deed
228. Transfer on Death
229. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = OK THEN:
230. Method of Transfer: Probate and Non-Probate
231. Decree of Distribution in Probate Court or
232. Trust or
233. Joint Tenancy or
234. Payable on Death Account
235. Method of Transfer: Small Estate Affidavit, Transfer on Death, Entity Agreements
236. Affidavit of Successor in Interest for personal not exceeding $50,000 or
237. Affidavit of Heirship for spendthrift trust not exceeding
238. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MD THEN:
239. You only need to show the death certificate of the deceased joint tenant or tenant by the entirety when a new deed is done.
240. There are no Transfer on Death Deeds in Maryland.  Note also that if any of the beneficiaries are minors, transfer can be done Uniform Transfers to Minors Act MD
241. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MI THEN:
242. Primary Method of Transfer: Tenants in Common
243. Documents evidencing the transfer include a Deed from the Personal Representatives of the Estate of the Deceased or a Court Order.
244. Primary Method of Transfer: Joint Tenants
245. Recording of a Certified Copy of the Death Certificate of the Deceased
246. Primary Method of Transfer: Tenancy by the Entireties
247. Recording of a Certified Copy of the Death Certificate for the Deceased spouse.
248. A deed from less than all tenants named in the instruments which created the tenancy will not be accepted as conveying full marketable title in the absence of record proof of the death of each such tenant who does not join the Deed.
249. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MA THEN:
250. Method of Transfer: Devise by Will
251. Order of Probate of the Will
252. A probate order court order of complete settlement of the estate for formal estate proceedings.
253. A sworn statement of the personal representative for informal estate proceedings
254. Method of transfer: Distribution in Kind from the Estate
255. Deed from the Personal Representative of the Estate
256. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = NJ THEN:
257. Method of Transfer: Probate (Unless property is held as joint tenants with right of survivorship)
258. Self-Proving Will
259. Certified Copy of Death Certificate
260. Deed
261. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = LA, KS, AL, AZ, AR, CA, CO, FL, IL, KS, GA, DE, MT, NE, NV, NM, ND
262. THEN:
263. If the method of transfer is non-probate:
264. If you were transferred the property by deed:
265. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = NM THEN:
266. Affidavit of Surviving Spouse (signed by Surviving Spouse)
267. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MT THEN:
268. Recorded Beneficiary Deed and Proof of Death
269. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = NV THEN:
270. To effectuate a right of survivorship, a court proceeding or recorded affidavit with the county recorder.
271. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = LA THEN:
272. Judgement of Possession in a Succession Proceeding
273. Judgement of Possession in a Foreclosure
274. Judgement of Dation En Paiement
275. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = KS, NE THEN:
276. Transfer on Death Deed
277. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = NM THEN:
278. Transfer of Death on Deed (signed by owner of the property)
279. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = AL, AZ, AR, CA, CO, FL THEN:
280. Deed conveying the property to you , that is signed by the owner or grantor with survivorship provision
281. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = AL, AZ, AR, CA THEN:
282. Evidence that the borrower is your parent, spouse, or child. (Birth Certificate, Marriage License, Death Certificate, or affidavit)
283. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = GA THEN:
284. Deed (Usually a quit-claim deed, tenants in common or joint tenancy with right or survivorship)
285. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = IL, KS THEN:
286. Notice of Death Affidavit for a Transfer on Death Instrument
287. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = IL THEN:
288. A deed signed by all heirs of an estate along with proof of heirship entered by a court or bond in lieu of probate issued by a title company.
289. Proof that an Independent  Adminstrator conveyed property owned by an Estate without leave of court.
290. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = GA THEN:
291. If the method of transfer is yearÆs support:
292. Order for YearÆs support transferring property filed in superior court real estate records
293. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = AL, AZ, AR, CA, DE THEN:
294. If the property was transferred to an entity in which you have an ownership interest (LLC, LP, etc.):
295. Deed conveying the property to the entity
296. Affidavit affirming that you have an ownership in the entity, and
297. Evidence that the borrower is your parent, spouse, or child.
298. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = CA THEN:
299. If the property was transferred by an affidavit of Real Property of Small Value ($50,000 or less), a petition to determind succession to real property (estates of $150,000 or less) or a spousal property petition or a certified probate court order for
300. Affidavit (Court Form DE û 305)
301. Certified Copy of Court Order on Petition to Determine Succession (Court Form DE 315)
302. Certified Copy of Court Order on Spousal Property Petition (Court Form DE û 226)
303. Certified Court Order
304. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MS THEN:
305. If the Method of Transfer is Administration or Probate
306. ExecutorÆs Deed
307. Will
308. No deed is required if property is real property and is located in the county of probate/administration; ExecutorÆs deed is required if real property is outside of the county of probate.
309. Method of Transfer: Transfer by Affidavit
310. Affidavit
311. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = ME, LA, IA, CO, IN, KY, IA, KS, IL, CO, AL, AZ, CA, DE, MN, MT,  NE, NH, ND THEN:
312. If the method of transfer is probate:
313. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MT THEN:
314. Personal Representatives Deed (Please note a copy of the letters testamentary should be recorded along with the deed to show the personal representative have authority at the time the deed was executed)
315. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = NH, NY THEN:
316. Will
317. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = NH THEN:
318. If no will, a list of heirs provided by the administrator
319. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = NY THEN:
320. Trust naming relative as beneficiary
321. A real property deed naming spouse or children as beneficiaries
322. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = ME THEN:
323. Personal RepresentativeÆs Deed of Sale
324. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = NE THEN:
325. Deed of Distribution
326. F M960 (State Abbreviation) = ND THEN:
327. Personal Representatives Deed or
328. Certified copy of Letters of Appointment
329. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = LA THEN:
330. Judgement of Possession in a Succession Proceeding
331. Judgement of Possession in a Foreclosure
332. Judgement of Dation En Paiement
333. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = IA THEN:
334. Last Will and Testament (if testate decedent); Court Officer Deed from Personal Representative to Devisee(s), surviving spouse or heirs
335. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = CO, IN, KY THEN:
336. Recorded Personal Representatives Deed and Certified copy of court issued letters
337. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = CO, IN, KY THEN:
338. If the estate is a small estate (less than $50,000), a small estate affidavit can be used
339. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = OH THEN:
340. Order of the Probate Court and the filing of a Certificate of Transfer
341. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = OH THEN:
342. Method of Transfer: Transfer on Death Designation Affidavit
343. Transfer on Death Designation Affidavit and Affidavit of Confirmation
344. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = IA THEN:
345. If the method of transfer is a will or intestate succession:
346. Final report of Personal Representative
347. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = KS, IL, CO, NV, AL, AZ, CA, DE, ND THEN:
348. If the method of transfer is probate:  (if no joint tenancy)
349. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = KS THEN:
350. Court Order and ExecutorÆs Deed
351. AdministratorÆs Deed
352. Decree of Descent
353. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = IL THEN:
354. Deed
355. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = CO THEN:
356. Recorded Decree determining heir and interest in real property (This process is used when normal probate has not occurred  and the deceased has left rela property that requires distribution.
357. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = NV THEN:
358. Letters of Testamentary or an Order admitted the will to Probate or Administration
359. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = AL, AZ, CA, NV THEN:
360. Court order authorizing, directing, or approving final distribution of Estate and Deed
361. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = DE THEN:
362. Deed conveying the property to you, and
363. Evidence that the borrower is your parent, spouse, or child.  (Birth Certificate, Marriage License, Death Certificate, or affidavit)
364. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = ND THEN:
365. Method of Transfer: Joint Tenancy
366. Record certified copies of Death Certificate
367. Affidavit of Death
368. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MN THEN:
369. Method of Transfer: Informal Testacy and Appointment Proceedings
370. If Testate:
371. Certified Copy of Unrestricted Letters Testamentary
372. Certified Copy of Will
373. Certified copy of Statement of Informal Probate of Will
374. Personal  RepresentativeÆs Deed of Distribution (together with consent of surviving spouse)
375. If Intestate:
376. Certified Copy of Unrestricted Letters of General Administration
377. Certified Copy of RegistrarÆs Statement Determining heirs of Decedent
378. Setting forth the name relationship and interest or fractional share of each heir in the property
379. Personal RepresentativeÆs Deed of Distribution in accordance with Registrars Determination
380. Method of Transfer: Formal Testacy and Appointment Proceedings with Unsupervised Administration
381. If Testate:
382. Certified Copy of Unrestricted Letters of Testamentary in full force and effect
383. Certified Copy of Probate Court Order
384. Certified Copy of Will
385. Personal Representatives Deed of Distribution in accordance with Registrars Determination
386. Method of Transfer: Formal Testacy and Appointment Proceedings with Supervised Administration
387. Certified Copy of Letter
388. Certified Copy of Order of Distribution
389. Personal Representatives Deed of Distribution
390. Certified Copy of Decree of Distribution
391. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = AL, AZ, AR, CA, CO, DE, FL, GA, ID, IL, IN, IA, KS, KY, LA, ME, MD, MA, MI, MN, MS, MT, NV, NH, NJ, NM, NY, NC, ND, OH, OK, OR, PA, RI,SC,  SD, TN, TX, UT, VT,VA, WA, WV,WI,WY THEN:
392. A transfer where the spouse or children of the borrower become an owner of the property.
393. To prove borrowerÆs death:
394. Death Certificate
395. To prove your identity:
396. Government Issued ID
397. To prove that you were transferred an ownership interest in the borrowerÆs property:
398. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = WY THEN:
399. Method of Transfer: Declaration of Trust, Affidavit of Survivorship, Deed with Life Estate
400. Trust or
401. Deed or
402. Affidavit of Survivorship with certified copy of Death Certificate
403. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = VA THEN
404. Method of Transfer: Probate, Summary Probate
405. Will or
406. Decree of Distribution or
407. Decree of Summary Distribution
408. Method of Transfer: Probate, List of Heirs filed with Circuit Court Clerk, Revocable Trust
409. Probate will or
410. File statutory list of heirs or
411. File Certificate of Trust
412. Method of Transfer: Transfer of Death Deed
413. Will or
414. List of Heirs or
415. Deed from Successor Trustee or
416. Transfer on Death Deed
417. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = WI THEN
418. Method of Transfer: Nonprobate
419. Deed executed by Grantor
420. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = WV THEN
421. Method of Transfer: Joint Tenants with the Right of Survivorship and Elective Share Action
422. Deed or
423. Marriage Certificate or
424. Petition for Elective Share and Deed
425. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = VT THEN
426. Method of Transfer: Probate
427. Deed and Death Certificate
428. Method of Transfer: Non-probate
429. Probate Court Order
430. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = TN THEN
431. Method of Transfer: Deed for Real Estate, Bill of Sale for Personal Property
432. Deed
433. Bill of Sale
434. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = RI, SD,TX, UT, WA THEN
435. Method of Transfer: Non-Probate
436. Deed signed by owner as transferor(assuming inter-vivos transfer)
437. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = WA THEN
438. Deed signed by  ôattorney in factö named  in General or Special power of attorney
439. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = SC THEN
440. Method of Transfer: Non-Probate
441. Deed Conveying title to husband and wife as ôjoint tenants with right of survivorship and not as tenants in commonö
442. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = PA THEN
443. Method of Transfer: Probate
444. Will
445. Deed
446. Probate Documents (Letters) and Notice of Appraisal from Department of Revenue as proof Inheritance Tax was paid
447. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = OR THEN
448. Method of Transfer: Nonprobate
449. Deed signed by owner as grantor (assuming inter-vivos transfer, if transfer is due to death of borrower)
450. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = OK THEN
451. Method of Transfer: Probate or Non-Probate by Affidavit or Contractual Agreement
452. Decree of Distribution (either by Will or Intestate Succession) or
453. Joint Tenancy Deed & Affidavit of Surviving Join Tenant with death certificate attached (with survivorship clause) or
454. Payable on Death Clause for intangible accounts or
455. Trust
456. Method of Transfer: Small Estate Affidavits or Transfer on Death Deed
457. Affidavit of Successor in Interest for personal property not exceeding $50,000 or
458. Transfer on Death Deed
459. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = OH THEN
460. Method of Transfer: Deed
461. Deed
462. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MD THEN:
463. Method of Transfer: Deed
464. Deed û The personal representative of the estate needs to present to the clerk of the Circuit Court û deed must recite the personal representativeÆs position and the estateÆs case number.
465. Certificate of Preparation û All MD Deeds must be signed by a MD lawyer or a party to the dead.
466. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MI THEN:
467. Primary Method of Transfer: Tenants in Common
468. Documents evidencing the transfer include a Deed from the Personal Representatives of the Estate of the Deceased or a Court Order.
469. Primary Method of Transfer: Joint Tenants
470. Recording of a Certified Copy of the Death Certificate of the Deceased.
471. Primary Method of Transfer: Tenancy by the Entireties
472. Recording of a Certified Copy of the Death Certificate for the Deceased spouse.
473. A deed from less than all tenants named in the instruments which created the tenancy will not be accepted as conveying full marketable title in the absence of record proof of the death of each such tenant who does not join the Deed.
474. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = NY THEN:
475. Method of Transfer: Court Order/ Probate
476. Will, Trust or other document naming spouse or children as beneficiaries
477. Real Property Deed
478. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MA THEN:
479. Method of Transfer: Deed
480. Deed executed by the grantor, describing the land conveyed, the consideration and containing an acknowledgement before a notary public.
481. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = ME, MN, ME, LA, KS, AL, AZ, AR, CA, FL, IL, ID, MS, MT, NC THEN:
482. If the primary method of transfer was non-probate:
483. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MS THEN:
484. Deed signed by owner as grantor if inter-vivos transfer
485. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MT THEN:
486. Beneficiary Deed
487. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = NC THEN:
488. Deed signed by Owner as Grantor
489. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = ME THEN:
490. Legal Description
491. Recording information establishing Joint-Tenancy
492. Names of Deceased and Surviving Tenants
493. Certified Copy of Death Certificate
494. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = NM THEN:
495. Affidavit of Surviving Spouse(Singed by Surviving Spouse)
496. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = LA THEN:
497. Judgement of Possession in a Succession Proceeding
498. Act of Sale
499. Act of Donation
500. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = KS, MN THEN:
501. Transfer on Death Deed
502. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = AL, AZ, AR, CA, FL, IL THEN:
503. Deed signed by the owner
504. Evidence that the borrower is your parent, spouse, or child. (Birth Certificate, Marriage License, Death Certificate, or affidavit)
505. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = ID, MN THEN:
506. Affidavit of Survivorship
507. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MN THEN:
508. Affidavit of Identity and Survivorship
509. Medical Assistance Clearance
510. Deed from grantor to grantee
511. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = AL, AZ, AR, CA, FL, IL THEN:
512. If the property was transferred to an entity in which you have an ownership interest (LLC, LP, etc.):
513. Deed conveying the property to the entity
514. Affidavit affirming that you have an ownership in the entity, and
515. Evidence that the borrower is your parent, spouse, or child.
516. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = DE THEN:
517. If you were transferred the property by deed (assuming intervivos transfer, if transfer is due to death contact TFS staff and request notice of transfer by death or operation of law):
518. Deed conveying the property to you, that is signed by the owner or grantor with survivorship provision
519. Evidence that the borrower is your parent, spouse, or child.  (Birth Certificate, Marriage License, Death Certificate, or affidavit)
520. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = FL, MN, LA, FL, ID, IA, IN, KY, MS, NH, MT, ND THEN:
521. If the method of transfer is probate:
522. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MS THEN:
523. Administration or Probate (if testamentary)
524. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MT THEN:
525. Personal Representatives Deed (Please note that a copy of letters of testamentary should be recorded along with the deed to show the personal representative have authority at the time the deed was executed.
526. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = ND THEN:
527. Personal RepresentativeÆs Deed
528. Certified copy of Letters of Appointment
529. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MN THEN:
530. Certified Copy of Decree of Descent
531. Transfer on Death Deed
532. Affidavit of identity and Surviviorship
533. Medical Assistance Clearance
534. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = LA THEN:
535. Judgement of Possession in a Succession Proceeding
536. Act of Sale
537. Act of Donation
538. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = FL, ID THEN:
539. Letters of Testamentary or an Order admitted the will to Probate or Administration
540. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = IA THEN:
541. Last Will and Testament (if testate decendent); Court Officer Deed from Personal Representative to Devisee(s), surviving spouse or heirs
542. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = FL, ID, IN, KY THEN:
543. Personal Representatives Deed
544. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = IN THEN:
545. If the estate is a small (less than $50,000), a small estate affidavit can be used
546. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = ND THEN:
547. Method of Transfer is Warranty Deed:
548. Deed with reserved life estate
549. Joint Tenancy
550. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = IA THEN:
551. If the method of transfer is a will or intestate succession:
552. Final report of Personal Representative
553. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = GA, KS THEN:
554. If the method of transfer is probate or administration:
555. Executors Deed or
556. Administrators Deed referencing probate court proceedings
557. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = NJ THEN:
558. Method of Transfer: Probate (Unless property is held as joint tenants with right of survivorship)
559. Self-Proving Will
560. Cerftified Copy of Death Certificate
561. Deed
562. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = KY THEN:
563. If the method of transfer is Joint Tenancy with a Right of Survivorship:
564. Death Certificate
565. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = NV THEN:
566. Method of Transfer: Judicial Set Aside Procedure
567. A court order to set aside property to minor children or a surviving spouse if the total estate is $100,000 or less.
568. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = AL, AZ, AR, CA, CO, DE, FL, GA, ID, IL, IN, IA, KS, KY, LA, ME, MD, MA, MI, MN, MS, MT, NE, NV, NH, NM, NY, NC, ND, OH, OK, OR, PA, RI, SC, SD, TN, TX, UT, VT, VA, WA, WV,WI,WY THEN:
569. Transfer to a spouse resulting from a divorce decree of a dissolution of marriage, legal separatioin agreement, or from an incidental property settlement agreement.
570. To prove your identity:
571. Government Issued ID
572. To prove that there was a divorce or separation:
573. Divorce Decree or
574. Decree of Legal Separation (Legal Separation may not be Recognized in your state)
575. To prove that you were transferred an ownership interest in the borrowerÆs property:
576. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = NY THEN:
577. Copy of the Decree or;
578. Separation Agreement or;
579. Court Order referencing the transfer of the property
580. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MI THEN:
581. Judgment of Divorce
582. Judgment of Separation Maintenance
583. Judgment of Annulment
584. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = ND THEN:
585. Summary Real Estate Disposition Judgment
586. Judgment of Divorce
587. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MD THEN:
588. Deed after Court Order
589. Property Settlement Agreement
590. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = IA, KS, ME, MN THEN:
591. Decree of Dissolution of Marriage
592. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = ME THEN:
593. Abstract of the Decree
594. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = IA, KS THEN:
595. Deed by relinquishing spouse
596. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = KY THEN:
597. Recorded Deed
598. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = WY THEN:
599. Method of Transfer: Decree of Divorce
600. Quitclaim Deed
601. Method of Transfer: Order signed by the judge and filed in the recorderÆs office
602. Wyoming Rules of Civil Procedure-Rule 70 Order signed by Judge Vesting Title in the Spouse
603. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = VA THEN:
604. Method of Transfer: Deed
605. Recorded Deed
606. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = WI THEN:
607. Method of Transfer: Non-probate
608. Deed executed by Grantor
609. Method of Transfer: Probate
610. Certified copy of portion of judgment of divorce affecting title or
611. A deed consistent with judgment
612. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = WV THEN:
613. Method of Transfer: Final Dispositive Order
614. Deed
615. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = TN THEN:
616. Method of Transfer: Deed for Real Estate to implement Order, Bill of Sale for Personal Property
617. Deed
618. Bill of Sale
619. Method of Transfer: Certified Copy of Order
620. Certified Copy of Order
621. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = RI SC, SD, UT, WA, VT, PA, OR THEN:
622. Method of Transfer: Non-Probate
623. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = RI SC, SD THEN:
624. Deed signed by owner as grantor
625. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = SC THEN:
626. A family court may direct the party execute and deliver a deed to carry out equitable appoitionment order.
627. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = UT THEN:
628. Deed signed by owner as grantor or
629. Deed signed by Court Clerk or another appointed person or
630. Certified Copy of Decree of Divorce
631. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = WA THEN:
632. Deed signed by owner as Grantor (Assuming inter-vivos transfer) or
633. Trust Instrument executed by owner identifying property as held in trust
634. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = VT THEN:
635. Quitclaim Deed
636. Divorce Decree
637. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = PA THEN:
638. Marital/Property Settlement Agreement and Deed
639. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = OR THEN:
640. Judgement of the court
641. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = OK THEN:
642. Method of Transfer: Court Order, Non- Probate
643. Judgement of District Court (A settlement agreement that is not incorporated in a decree and lacks a legal description will not convey title)
644. Method of Transfer: Automatic Revocation of Spousal Interest
645. Rather than a transfer, an extinction of a spousal interest as a beneficiary occurs upon divorce or annulment of rights under a will, trust, or contractual arrangement such as life insurance, annuities, retirement benefits, payable on death benefits
646. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = OH THEN:
647. If the property was transferred by deed, a copy of the deed of the deed transferring the property to you can serve as proof.
648. If a divorce decree or judgment affecting the property was issued by a court in a state other than the subject state, a copy of the deed transferring the property to you can serve as proof.
649. If you do not have a deed, but do have a divorce decree or decree of legal separation that includes specific language of conveyance of title to you, either a divorce decree or decree of legal separation can serve as proof.
650. If you do not have a deed, but do have a divorce decree or decree of legal separation that incorporates a separation and property settlement agreement and includes specific language of conveyance of title to you; then the Settlement agreement along w
651. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = NH THEN:
652. Method of Transfer: Superior Court Family Division
653. Quitclaim deed from one spouse to the other
654. Method of Transfer: Decree
655. Certified Copy of Court Decree Recorded at Registry of Deeds
656. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MA, MT, ND THEN:
657. Method of Transfer: Court Order or Decree
658. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) =MA THEN:
659. The recoding or registration of a duly certified copy of such decree, attested by the clerk, assistant clerk, register or assistant register, recorder or deputy recorder, as the case may be.
660. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MT THEN:
661. Court Order and Quit Claim Deed
662. Warranty Deed
663. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = ND THEN:
664. Quit Claim Deed
665. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MA THEN:
666. Method of Transfer: Deed by Order of the Court
667. Duly certified or attested copy of the judgment directing the grantor spouse to act.
668. Duly certified or attested copy of the order appointing another person to act for the grantor spouse.
669. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = NV THEN:
670. Method of Transfer: Deed or Court Order
671. Deed or court order is required to effectuate the transfer of title.
672. Method of Transfer: Informal Agreement
673. Informal Agreement (For real property where there is no court decree, a recorded deed is required to change title)
674. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = AL, AZ, AR, CA, CO, DE, FL, GA, ID, IL THEN:
675. Method of Transfer: Probate
676. If the property was transferred by deed, a copy of the deed transferring the property to you can serve as proof.
677. If a divorce decree or judgment affecting the property was issued by a court in a state other than the subject state, a copy of the deed transferring the property to you can serve as proof.
678. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = LA, KS, IN, AL, AZ, AR, CA, CO, DE, GA, ID, IL, IN, IA, KS, MS, NE THEN:
679. Method of Transfer: Non Probate
680. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = LA THEN:
681. Judgement of Partition
682. Acts of Partition
683. Acts of Sale
684. Quit Claim Deed
685. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = KS THEN:
686. Decree of Divorce (A property description should appear in both a Decree of Divorce and, when included, the property settlement agreement
687. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = IN THEN:
688. Deed signed by court appointed commissioner
689. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MS, NE, NJ, NC, TX THEN:
690. Deed signed by owner as grantor
691. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = TX THEN:
692. Filing of Certified Copy of Final Deceree of Divorce in the real property records
693. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = NM THEN:
694. Deed signed by owner of interest in property
695. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = NC THEN:
696. Deed signed by clerk of the court
697. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = AL, AZ, AR, CA, CO, DE, GA, ID THEN:
698. If you do not have a deed, but do have a divorce decree or decree of legal separation that includes specific language of conveyance of title to you, either a divorce decree or decree of legal separation can serve as proof.
699. If you do not have a deed, but do have a divorce decree or decree of legal separation that incorporates a separation and property settlement agreement and includes specific language of conveyance of title to you; then the Settlement agreement along w
700. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = AZ THEN:
701. Trust instrument executed by owner identifying property as held in trust by owner.
702. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = AL, AZ, AR, CA, CO, DE, FL, GA, IL, IN, IA, KS, MS, MT, NE, NV,NH,NJ, NM, NY, OH, OK, OR, PA, RI, SC, SD, TN, TX, UT, VT, VA, WA,WV,WI,WY THEN:
703. Note: In order to remove a borrower from the Original Note and become the sole owner. You would need to refinance the loan in your name only or pay off the mortgage loan entirely.
704. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = AL, AZ, AR, CA, CO, DE, FL, GA, ID, IL, IN, IA, KS, KY, LA, ME, MD, MA, MI, MN, MS, MT, NE, NV, NH, NJ, NM, NY, NC, ND, OH, OK, OR, PA, RI, SC, SD, TN, TX, UT, VT, VA,WA,WV,WI,WY THEN:
705. A transfer into an inter vivos trust in which the borrower is and remains a beneficiary and which does not relate to a transfer of rights of occupancy in the property
706. To prove your identity:
707. Valid Government Issued ID
708. To prove that you were transferred an ownership interest in the borrowerÆs property:
709. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = WY THEN:
710. Method of Transfer: Declaration of Trust
711. Warranty Deed from Settlor to Trustee
712. Method of Transfer: Certificate of Trust
713. Certificate of Trust
714. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = WI THEN:
715. Method of Transfer: Nonprobate
716. Deed executed by Grantor
717. Assignment of Property to Trust executed by Grantor.  (Trust can be created by declaration   WIS. Stat. 701.0401)
718. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = VA THEN:
719. Method of Transfer: Deed to Transfer Title into the Trustee of Revocable Trust
720. Record Deed
721. Transferring to Trustee for Estate planning purposes
722. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = VT THEN:
723. Method of Transfer: Non-probate
724. Deed of Trust Grantor/ Settlor to Trustee with reserved life estate and power of appointment (LBJ Deed)
725. Method of Transfer: Deed
726. Deed of Trust Grantor/Settlor to Trustee without reserved life estate and power of appointment
727. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = TN THEN:
728. Method of Transfer: Deed for Real Estate, Bill of Sale for Personal Property
729. Deed
730. Bill of Sale
731. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = RI, SC, SD, TX, UT,WA THEN:
732. Method of Transfer: Non-probate
733. Deed signed by owner as grantor
734. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = UT,WA THEN:
735. Trust Instrument executed by owner identifying property as held in trust
736. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = PA THEN:
737. Trust and Notice of Appraisal from Department of Revenue as proof Inheritance Tax was paid or
738. Deed indicating transfer of property from Trust to beneficiary and Notice of Appraisal from Department of Revenue as proof Inheritance Tax was paid
739. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = OR THEN:
740. Method of Transfer:Non-probate
741. Deed signed by owner to trustee(s) of the trust
742. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = OK THEN:
743. Method of Transfer: Conveyance, Non-probate
744. A trust holding real property must be written
745. A memorandum of Trust stating date of creation and the names of the trustee must be filed in the records of the county clerk where real property is located
746. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = NY THEN:
747. Method of Transfer: Transferor would only need paperwork indicating the property has been transferred
748. Real Property Deed transferring the property to the Trust
749. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = OH THEN:
750. Method of Transfer: Deed
751. Memorandum of Trust or
752. Deed
753. Method of Transfer: Certificate of Transfer from Probate Court
754. Order of the Probate Court and the filing of a Certificate of Transfer
755. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = WV THEN:
756. Method of Transfer: Deed
757. Revocable trust
758. Deed to Trust via Trustee and Memorandum of Trust
759. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MI THEN:,
760. Real estate may be conveyed to the Trustee of the Trust or the Trust by grantor(s) who own the real estate.
761. The Michigan statute of frauds prohibits an oral trust in real property.
762. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MD THEN:
763. Deed
764. Certificate of Trust must be presented to Circuit Court at time of recording the deed putting the property into the trust.
765. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = KY THEN:
766. Recorded Deed
767. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = IA THEN:
768. Warranty Deed
769. TrusteeÆs Affidavit by Individual Trustee (Iowa State Bar Association Official Form #113)
770. Corporate Trustee (Iowa  State Bar Association Official Form #114)
771. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = ND THEN:
772. Warranty Deed
773. Quitclaim Deed to Trust (May by revocable or irrevovable)
774. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = AL, AZ, AR, CA, CO, GA, ID, IL THEN
775. A deed or instrument that conveys the property into the trust, AND either a:
776. Trust Document and an affidavit signed or otherwise authenticated by the trustee that states the document has not been revoked, modified, or amended in any manner.
777. Certificate of Trust signed or otherwise authenticated by the trustee that states the trust has not been revoked, modified, or amended so as to render the certificate incorrect.
778. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = ID, IL THEN
779. Trust in Real Property that arose by implication or operation of law without a writing signed by the party granting the interest in the property.  If this is the case , provide evidence of such that is clear, statisfactory and convincing.
780. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MN, MT THEN
781. Method of Transfer û Probate:
782. Transfer on Death Deed
783. Affidavit of Identity and Survivorship
784. Certified Copy of Death
785. Medical Assistant Clearance Certificate
786. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MT THEN
787. Personal Representatives Deed (Please note a copy of the letters testamentary should be recorded along with the deed to show the personal representative have authority at the time the deed was executed)
788. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MA, NV, NH THEN
789. Method of Transfer: Deed
790. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = NH THEN:
791. Quitclaim Deed from Current Owners to Trustee
792. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = NV THEN:
793. Deed or equivalent is required to transfer title
794. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MA THEN:
795. Deed from the grantor/borrower either declaring that the borrower holds the real property in trust or to another person as trustee.
796. The settlor must have the capacity to create a trust and must indicate an intention to create the trust.  A definite beneficiary is required, and the trustee must have duties to perform.  To be actual, as opposed to merely a nominee trust or agency, 
797. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = NV THEN:
798. Method of Transfer: Written Declaration
799. One may declare property to be trust property without a formal transfer document
800. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = DE, LA, KS, MN, IN, ME, AL, AZ, AR, CA, CO, GA, ID THEN
801. To prove that you are and remain a beneficiary to the trust and the transfer into the trust does not relate to a transfer of rights of occupancy in the property:
802. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = LA, KS, MN, DE, IN, MT, NC, NE THEN
803. Method of Transfer û Non Probate:
804. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = NE THEN
805. Deed signed by settlor
806. Declaration by owner of property
807. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = NC THEN
808. Deed signed by owner as grantor
809. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = LA THEN
810. Acts of Sales
811. Acts of Donations to the Trust
812. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = KS THEN
813. Deed from Borrower to Trust
814. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MN THEN
815. Deed from grantor to trustee
816. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = DE, IN, NJ THEN
817. Deed signed by owner as grantor
818. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MS THEN
819. Deed to Trustee accompanied by Trust
820. Memorandum/ Certificate of Trust
821. Will
822. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = MT THEN
823. Recorded Beneficiary Deed and Proof of Death
824. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = NM THEN
825. Method of Transfer: Non-probate and Probate
826. Deed signed by grantor or personal representative
827. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = ME THEN
828. Method of Transfer: Non-Probate(In Maine, the probate court has jurisdiction regardless)
829. Simple deed from Borrower to Trustee and Incorporating Trust Document (Both of which should be recorded)
830. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = AL, AZ, AR, CA, CO, GA, ID, IN THEN
831. An affidavit signed by the trustee stating:
832. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = AL, AZ, AR, CA, CO, GA, ID THEN
833. The identities of all present beneficiaries
834. That you are and remain a beneficiary to the trust and
835. The transfer of the property into the trust does not relate to a transfer of rights of occupancy in the property.
836. IF M960 (State Abbreviation) = IN THEN
837. A person may create a custodial trust of property by a written transfer of the property to another person.  This can be evidenced by registration of the property OR by an instrument of transfer.
838. Please review the circumstances listed above, and provide us with the appropriate documentation for the option that best describes your situation via fax to <CSFax>, email to <CSEmail>, or by mail to:
839. <CompanyLongName>
840. <CompanyReturnAddr1>
841. <CompanyReturnAddr2>
842. <CompanyReturnAddr3>
843. You may obtain a more individualized description of required documents by providing additional information. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this request, please contact our Customer Service Department at <CSPhoneNumber>. Our office is
844. Sincerely,
845. Customer Service Department
846. <CompanyLongName>
